Forrest J Ackerman Papers
Forrest J Ackerman Papers
- Science fiction
  - Literary material
    - Planet Stories Vol. 4 #9 "Mars Is Hell", Nov, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Science Fiction Digest
      - Vol. 2 #1 "Philip Wylie", Sep, 1933 (Box 6)
      - Vol. 2 #2 "Scientificinematorially Speaking", Oct, 1933 (Box 6)
      - Vol. 2 #4 "He Wrote 'Souls Aspace'"; "Science Fiction Fun"; "Scientificinematorially Speaking"; "Six Startling Scientifilms", Dec, 1933 (Box 6)
    - Spaceway
      - Vol. 1 #2 "Scientifilm Parade", Feb, 1954 (Box 6)
      - Vol. 1 #3 "Scientifilm Parade", Apr, 1954 (Box 6)
      - Vol. 2 #1 "Scientifilm Parade", Jun, 1950 (Box 6)
      - Vol. 2 #2 "Scientifilm Parade", Dec, 1954 (Box 6)
      - Vol. 2 #3 "Scientifilm Parade", Feb, 1955 (Box 6)
    - Super-Science Stories, "Dhactwho-Remember?" by Ackerman, Forrest J. and Morley, Wilifred Owen; both British and American editions, 2 books (Box 7)
    - Thrilling Wonder Stories Vol. 14 #2 "Looking Forward", Oct, 1939 (Box 7)
    - Utopian Vol. 1 #6 (no. 199 limited to 300 copies) "Pre-Hysteric", Jun, 1952 (Box 7)
    - V59, "Ces Amours de Monstres"; "L'Auteur, Tel Qu'il se Voit"; "Tina Petit", undated (Box 7)
    - Weird Tales Vol. 34 #6 "Nymph of Darkness" by Ackerman, Forrest J and Moore, C. L., Dec, 1939 (Box 7)
    - Wonder Stories Vol. 7 #8 "Earth's Lucky Day" by Ackerman, Forrest J and Flagg, F.; "The Reader Speaks"; "Science Fiction League", Apr, 1936 (Box 7)
  - Published material
    - Booklets
      - Tricks beleben den Film by Unbehaun, Klaus autographed, undated (Box 7)
    - Clippings
      - 1956-1967, undated (Box 7)
      - "The Challenge from Beyond", undated (Box 7)
    - Magazines
      - Los Cuentos Fantasticos
        - Tomo II, Jul 15, 1948 (Box 8)
        - Tomo III, Jul 31, 1948 (Box 8)
        - Tomo IV, Aug 15-31, 1948 (Box 8)
        - #5, Sep 1-15, 1948 (Box 8)
        - #6, Sep 16-30, 1948 (Box 8)
        - #7, Oct 1-15, 1948 (Box 8)
        - #8, Oct 16-31, 1948 (Box 8)
        - Vol. 1 #9, #13, undated (Box 8)
        - Vol. 2 #16, #17, #18, #19, #20, #21, #23, #24, undated (Box 8)
        - Vol. 3 #27, #28, #29, #30, #31, #32, #34, #35, undated (Box 8)
        - Vol. 4 #37, #39, #40, #41, #42, #43, #44, undated (Box 8)
      - Haunted Vol. #1, Mar, 1963 (Box 8)
      - Vectors Vol. 4 #4, 4th Quarter, 1962 (Box 8)
- 1978 additions
  - Art
    - Commercial (Box 1)
    - Etchings, 10 folders (Box 1)
    - Paintings, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Photographs (Box 1)
    - Photographs, 5 folders (Box 2)
  - Clippings
    - Miscellaneous, 12 folders (Box 2)
  - Correspondence
    - Business, 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Business, 22 folders (Box 3)
    - Business, 22 folders (Box 4)
    - Business, 24 folders (Box 5)
    - Business, 25 folders (Box 6)
    - Business, 25 folders (Box 7)
    - Cards (Box 8)
    - Cards (Box 9)
    - Cards (Box 10)
    - Fan mail, 22 folders (Box 11)
    - Fan mail, 22 folders (Box 12)
    - Fan mail, 22 folders (Box 13)
    - Fan mail, 22 folders (Box 14)
    - Fan mail, 22 folders (Box 15)
    - Fan mail, 22 folders (Box 16)
    - Fan mail, 28 folders (Box 17)
    - Fan mail, postcards, telegrams (Box 18)
    - General, 22 folders (Box 19)
    - General, 23 folders (Box 20)
    - General, 23 folders (Box 21)
    - General, 24 folders (Box 22)
    - General, 23 folders (Box 23)
    - Publicity, 18 folders (Box 24)
    - Publicity, 20 folders (Box 25)
    - Publicity, 20 folders (Box 26)
    - Publicity, 20 folders (Box 27)
    - Publicity, 20 folders (Box 28)
    - Publicity, 20 folders (Box 29)
    - Publicity, 10 folders (Box 30)
  - Film art
    - [miscellaneous] (Oversize 1)
  - Fragments
    - [miscellaneous], 10 folders (Box 30)
    - [miscellaneous], 21 folders (Box 31)
    - [miscellaneous], 20 folders (Box 32)
    - [miscellaneous], 20 folders (Box 33)
  - General
    - Miscellany, 18 folders (Box 34)
  - Memorabilia
    - [miscellaneous], 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Memoranda
    - [miscellaneous], 14 folders (Box 36)
  - Publications
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous, 16 folders (Box 37)
  - Photographs
    - Personal (Box 3)
    - Nude portraits (Box 38)
  - Records
    - Financial, 20 folders (Box 38)
    - Financial, 12 folders (Box 39)
    - Personal
      - Address books, 5 volumes (Box 39)
      - Business cards (Box 40)
      - Letterhead (Box 41)
      - Note cards, 7 folders (Box 41)
  - Social events
    - [miscellaneous], 11 folders (Box 41)
    - [miscellaneous], 17 folders (Box 42)
    - Pamphlets, 10 items (Box 42)
    - Pamphlets, 62 items (Box 43)
  - Unsolicited mail
    - [miscellaneous] (Box 44-58)
  - Writings
    - Typescripts, by Ackerman
      - Creepy, Eerie, Spacemen and Vampirella (Box 59)
      - Famous Monsters of Filmland, 7 folders (Box 59)
      - Imagination (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous, 7 folders (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 60)
    - Published, by Ackerman
      - Assorted works (Box 60)
      - Famous Monsters of Filmland, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Typescripts, miscellaneous
      - Books, assorted, 5 folders (Box 61)
      - Books, assorted, 6 folders (Box 62)
      - Perry Rhodan, complete, 10 folders (Box 61)
      - Perry Rhodan, complete, 16 folders (Box 62)
      - Perry Rhodan, complete, 5 folders (Box 63)
      - Perry Rhodan, fragments, 2 folders (Box 63)
      - Speeches and commentaries (Box 63)
      - Short stories and poems, 9 folders (Box 63)
      - Short stories and poems, fragments; 3 folders (Box 64)
      - Galley proofs, The Beast, by A. E. Van Vogt (Box 64)
      - Published works, miscellaneous (Box 64)
- 1991 additions
  - Essays
    - "A Brush with Genius," Omni (Box 1)
  - Periodicals
    - Filmfax, Feb-Sep 1991; 4 issues (Box 1)
    - Monsterama, May 1991 (Box 1)
  - Memorabilia
    - [miscellaneous] (Box 1)
  - Clippings
    - Articles about (Box 1)
  - Videotape
    - [unidentified], 1990 (Box 1)